# **MARIGI MANUEL IRESA**

#### **CONTACT**

👪 Kasarani, Nairobi, Kenya.

**L** +254 742 929 685

**3/06/1997** 

**in** https://www.linkedin.com/in/marigimanuel-b731a1181

# **OBJECTIVE**

Obtain a challenging leadership position applying creative problem solving and lean management skills with a growing company to achieve optimum utilization of its resources and maximum profits.

#### **SKILLS**

- Web Development and Design.
- Workplace safety and health -St. John Ambulance.
- First Aid skills.
- PHP, Javascrip, Bootstrap, MYSQL, etc.
- Estimable interpersonal skills.
- Superior leadership skills.
- Project coordination.
- Avid research skills.
- Insistent in time management.

#### **INTERESTS**

- Reading nonfiction books.
- Listening to environmental and economic debates.
- Following wildlife documentaries.
- Motivation advice.
- Nature walks.
- Socializing with family.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- ✓ English.
- ✓ Kiswahili.

#### **REFERENCE**

• Dr. Lewis Sitoki. - Chairperson, Department of Geoscience and The Environment.

The Technical University of Kenya.



#### **PROFILE STATEMENT**

A conscientious, honest, and fiercely competitive graduate of Bachelor of Technology in Environmental Resource Management. I have excellent leadership skills, having been actively involved in leadership responsibilities at several stages of my academic journey. With tremendous experience in online writing and research, I have developed a meticulous, customerfocused approach to work and a solid drive to see things through to completion.

#### **EDUCATION**

<b>Institute of Software Development.</b> Diploma in Software Development. Awaiting Completion.	2022 - 2023
<b>Institute of Software Development.</b> Certificate in Software Development. A	2021 - 2022
The Technical University of Kenya.  Bachelor of Technology in Environmental Resource  Management.  Second Class Honours, Lower Division.	2016 - 2021
<b>Ikerege Secondary School.</b> Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (KCSE). B (plain).	2012 - 2015
Masangora Primary School.	2007 - 2011

#### **EXPERIENCE**

334 out of 500.

### Self Employed.

Online Writing.

Submitting countless research papers with a 100% approval rate.

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education (KCPE).

Ensuring maximum client satisfaction with excellent ability to pay unparalleled attention to detail, deadlines, and writing integrity.

# **Kenya Forest Service.** Industrial Attachment.

Dec 2020 - Feb

2018 - Present.

2021

Excelled in forest extension services.

Natural forests management.

Office management.

Agro-ecological significance of forests, among other critical areas.

# Independent Electoral and Boundaries Commision, IEBC.

August 2017 -October 2017

Polling Clerk.

+254 786 353 622

Verified voters' authenticity using the Kenya Integrated Election Management System (KIEMS).

Maintained the secrecy of the ballot.

Performed any other duties prescribed by the Returning Officer.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS**

 $\checkmark$  Youth Championship, Regional environmental activism -best essay in environmental conservation remedies.